<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?> 
<ModMetaData>
     <name>[tW] YAAM - Yet Another Agriculture Mod</name>
     <author>theWul</author>
     <targetVersion>0.18.0</targetVersion>
     <description>
          
Of course there are quite some other mods offering a broad range of terraforming, but I wanted a somewhat different gameplay experience:
     * simple, but respecting research progression
     * close to vanilla
     * add an "agriculture" gameplay element: by default the improved terrains are converted back to normal soil after harvesting, leaving a blueprint to improve the terrain again.
       Theres a mod option to completely turn off this conversion behaviour. 
       If conversion is turned on, blueprint placing can be toggled for each growing zone individually.
     * add buttons to growing zone UI to quickly place blueprints for the whole zone (of course only where fertility is lower)
     
New research: Composting

New items and buildings:
     * raw compost:
          Organic stuff giving the "... has rotted away in storage" message now converts into "raw compost".
          Can be crafted at the crafting spot from any nutrients.
          Can be used in a composter, burned or disposed somewhere.
     * compost:
          obviously "composting" research required
          produced in one of the available composters
          > compost bin: 
               easy to build from wood, but its efficiency depends on temperature
          > industrial composter:
               as long as power is available temperature independent
               "electricity" required   
     * fertilizer:
          "drug production" required
          produced at the drug labor
          2 compost -> 1 fertilizer

New terrains (enhanced soils need a growable terrain to build, work is? balanced for the remove-soil-after-harvest behaviour):
     * normal soil:
          lots of work to build, allows to convert any dry terrain to vanilla soil
     * tilled soil: 
          fertility: 1.2
     * enriched soil: 
          fertility: 1.4 (equal to rich soil)
     * fertilized soil:
          fertility: 2.0
      
     * two higher contrast textures for mud and gravel (delete "patches.xml" in the mods "patches" folder if you don't like 'em).

Compatibility:
     * can be added to existing saves
     * removal from existing saves is somewhat unpredictable as long as any of the added terrains, items or buildings are on the map
     * other mods: 
       - should work with everything out there 
       - the patching of food decay should be technically safe (thanks to harmony) but may lead to unintuitve results with other mods doing the same 
     
Credits:
     * Rainbeau Flambe and his "Fertile Fields" mod, which actually got me started
     * everybody uploading their mods to github

Source: https://github.com/theWul/-tw-Mods
</description>
</ModMetaData>

